Fill it Forward Application  
Privacy Policy
============================================

Updated as of April 20, 2020

Fill it Forward  is a brand of Green Menu Inc. We respect the privacy rights of our online and mobile users and customers and recognize the importance of protecting the information we collect. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Green Menu Inc. and Fill it Forward (“Fill it Forward”, “we” or “Company”) including the Fill it Forward mobile applications, fillitforward.com, and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by Fill it Forward or Green Menu Inc. (collectively, the “Services”).

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain what information we collect from our users when they interact with our Services, including what personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information we collect, how to use that information, with whom we share that information and what steps we take to protect that information. Our Services are hosted in the United States and if you are accessing them from outside the United States, please be advised that you are transferring information to the United States. Your continued use of our Services represents your consent to this transfer of information.

By visiting fillitforward.com and installing the Fill it Forward application you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions. You should not use the Services if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Services represents your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

If you are under the age of 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about Fill it Forward’s Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions as well as attain their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions before registering or placing an order with Fill it Forward.

### 2\. Information Collection and Use by Fill it Forward

Fill it Forward users are required to register before they can use most of Fill it Forward services. During registration, Fill it Forward collects certain personally identifiable information which is information that personally identifies users, such as name and email address.

Fill it Forward also collects certain information that does not personally identify users. This non-personally identifiable information includes certain demographic information we collect about users such as age, gender, and location. Fill it Forward does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 and if we learn that we have collected such information Fill it Forward takes steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

Fill it Forward tracks the ways that users interact with the Services and will collect information regarding such interaction. The information Fill it Forward may collect when users interact with the Services includes IP address, ISP, browser type, operating system, language, profile information, water, foods and exercise tracked, weight and general user activity on Fill it Forward. Personal data collected from you may be shared with third-party providers of Fill it Forward that process personal data on behalf of Fill it Forward such as server hosting providers, data storage providers, analytics service providers, and payment service providers. Fill it Forward will always apply safeguards to protect your personal data from unauthorized disclosure.

Fill it Forward may share information (both personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information) if Fill it Forward is required to do so by applicable law or if Fill it Forward has a good faith belief that sharing information is necessary to comply with applicable law.

Fill it Forward may from time to time share non-personally identifiable information with our affiliates and advertisers and other third-parties. Fill it Forward may also use your information to personalize the Services and improve the operation and functionality of our Services.

### 3\. Information Tracking

Fill it Forward and any of our other advertisements or email messages may contain “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags. These technologies help us better customize our Service to users and to facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements or messages. Fill it Forward does not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information submitted. Furthermore, most browsers allow users to disable cookies.

### 4\. Information Security

Fill it Forward takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of user personal data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

Fill it Forward restricts access to user personal information to our employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution if they fail to meet these obligations.

Despite our efforts regarding data security, no system can be 100% secure and there is always a risk of unauthorized access to your personal data. By using our Services, you assume this risk. We also urge you to use a unique and strong password to your user account on Fill it Forward Services as well as to protect such password.

### 5\. Links

Fill it Forward may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. This privacy policy only governs information collected on Fill it Forward.

### 6\. Children

If you are under the age of  13, you are not allowed to submit any personal data through our Services. Further, we encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet use and to help us in enforcing our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide any personal data through our Service without their permission. If you become aware that a child under the age of 18 has submitted personal data to us, please contact us at [info@fillitforward.com](mailto:info@fillitforward.com)

### 7\. Marketing

Fill it Forward may use your personal data for profiling and marketing purposes via emails, notifications, or other messages. Profiling will be used for marketing purposes to enable personalized and relevant offers to you, based on your preferences. The use of personal data for marketing purposes will only concern such offers that have a close relation to your use of the Service and the offers will be sent to you by Fill it Forward; no personal data will be transferred to third parties for marketing purposes.

In case you do not want Fill it Forward to use your personal data for the purpose of marketing, you may at any time unsubscribe from any further messages by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of such a message or emailing us at [info@fillitforward.com](mailto:info@fillitforward.com).

### 8\. Notifications

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business-related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, through conspicuous posting of such notice on our website page or sending push notifications on your mobile devices, as determined by us in our sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt-out of certain means of notification such as unsubscribing from emails or turning off the push notifications inside the mobile app.

### 9\. HIPPA

We are not a “covered entity” under the U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (“HIPAA”). The HIPAA privacy rules and regulations apply to health plans, health care clearinghouses, any health care provider who transmits health information in electronic form in connection with transactions for which the Secretary of HHS has adopted standards under HIPAA (collectively, “covered entities”), and their service providers (“business associates”). This means that the personal data that you provide to us is not protected by the HIPAA privacy rules and regulations.

### 10\. Updating or Removing Information

Fill it Forward users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by emailing our technical support team at [info@fillitforward.com](mailto:info@fillitforward.com).

### 11\. Portability

You have the right to receive your personal data which you have provided Fill it Forward, in accordance with relevant personal data regulation, provided that such request does not adversely affect the right and freedoms of others.

### 12\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may need to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Therefore, we reserve the right to update and/or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to you. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. Please review this Privacy Policy frequently, and especially before you register an account with us. The date of the last modification is listed at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

### 13\. Contacting Fill it Forward

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or Fill it Forward please contact us at [info@fillitforward.com](mailto:info@fillitforward.com)

Last Updated: 04/20/2020

Access the Fill it Forward Application Terms of Use here: [Terms of Use](https://www.fillitforward.com/fill-it-forward-app-terms-of-use/)
